const data = [
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "The three students study in the same program, BA in Spanish and Literature.",
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Antonio introduces Marcela to Johnny.",
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Introduction to technology is one of the subjects they study.",
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Marcela asks Johnny to repeat the name of the classroom they have class in.",
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Johnny says that He and Antonio are in the same class.",
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Johnny does not have class at “La Julita”.",
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Marcela and Antonio do not have Educational Informatics class together. ",
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Marcela has class at 10:00 a.m. on Tuesdays.",
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Antonio is not interested in his program.",
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Johnny needs to walk very much to go to one of his classes.",
        "answer": true
    }
]

export default data